[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"], "LOCATION": ["Shemp"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "And why he compares the GOP field to the Three Stooges?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "he", "compares", "the", "GOP", "field", "to", "the", "Three", "Stooges", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "Actually I was just thinking of your analogy, I was thinking Ron Paul is sort of a Shemp.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", "I", "was", "just", "thinking", "of", "your", "analogy", ",", "I", "was", "thinking", "Ron", "Paul", "is", "sort", "of", "a", "Shemp", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "Are you -- are you a funny person by nature?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "a", "funny", "person", "by", "nature", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "As is evidenced by this interview no.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "is", "evidenced", "by", "this", "interview", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Was that one of the most extraordinary experiences in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "one", "of", "the", "most", "extraordinary", "experiences", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't say extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Booker"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "It was a long day, it was full of -- a lot of celebration as well as grief, but how would you describe it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "long", "day", ",", "it", "was", "full", "of", "--", "a", "lot", "of", "celebration", "as", "well", "as", "grief", ",", "but", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "You -- it was really not just a long day but it was a day full of family, full of friends, full of people from the industry, from the government, Governor Christie, Mayor Booker.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "--", "it", "was", "really", "not", "just", "a", "long", "day", "but", "it", "was", "a", "day", "full", "of", "family", ",", "full", "of", "friends", ",", "full", "of", "people", "from", "the", "industry", ",", "from", "the", "government", ",", "Governor", "Christie", ",", "Mayor", "Booker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "How big a blow do you think it was to her that she lost the power of her voice and couldn't hit the great notes she used to hit?", "question_tokens": ["How", "big", "a", "blow", "do", "you", "think", "it", "was", "to", "her", "that", "she", "lost", "the", "power", "of", "her", "voice", "and", "could", "n't", "hit", "the", "great", "notes", "she", "used", "to", "hit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "You know, to any singer, that would be devastating.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "to", "any", "singer", ",", "that", "would", "be", "devastating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "For you, what did you think?", "question_tokens": ["For", "you", ",", "what", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Well, I think with all these cases, it's a matter of she paid the price for what she thought she used to want.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "with", "all", "these", "cases", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "matter", "of", "she", "paid", "the", "price", "for", "what", "she", "thought", "she", "used", "to", "want", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Do you know anything about that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "anything", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, it's not illegal to be a party girl.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "illegal", "to", "be", "a", "party", "girl", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "How did she change from the woman you saw?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "she", "change", "from", "the", "woman", "you", "saw", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Well, physically, she changed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "physically", ",", "she", "changed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Drew"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Partly but addiction is not as Dr. Drew, who treated me, by the way, successfully, it's not about -- it's not a character defect, it's not a moral problem, it's, you know, something wrong with your brain, to put it simply.", "answer_tokens": ["Partly", "but", "addiction", "is", "not", "as", "Dr.", "Drew", ",", "who", "treated", "me", ",", "by", "the", "way", ",", "successfully", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "about", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "character", "defect", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "moral", "problem", ",", "it", "'s", ",", "you", "know", ",", "something", "wrong", "with", "your", "brain", ",", "to", "put", "it", "simply", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Whitney just never seemed to have the desire to rehabilitate herself, to actually get proper treatment for this, did she?", "question_tokens": ["Whitney", "just", "never", "seemed", "to", "have", "the", "desire", "to", "rehabilitate", "herself", ",", "to", "actually", "get", "proper", "treatment", "for", "this", ",", "did", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "When you saw -- I don't know if you did see, but in the run-up to the day she died, for a few days, pictures emerging from Hollywood nightclubs of her falling out and looking disheveled and so on, did you fear that something awful would happen?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "you", "did", "see", ",", "but", "in", "the", "run-up", "to", "the", "day", "she", "died", ",", "for", "a", "few", "days", ",", "pictures", "emerging", "from", "Hollywood", "nightclubs", "of", "her", "falling", "out", "and", "looking", "disheveled", "and", "so", "on", ",", "did", "you", "fear", "that", "something", "awful", "would", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "'BRIEN: No.", "answer_tokens": ["'BRIEN", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Doesn't that ring alarm bells?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "that", "ring", "alarm", "bells", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Not really because I don't -- I don't know what she was doing and still we don't have the toxicology reports yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "she", "was", "doing", "and", "still", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "the", "toxicology", "reports", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "We don't now either way, right?", "question_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "now", "either", "way", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I think they've said no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'ve", "said", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Barely two weeks ago?", "question_tokens": ["Barely", "two", "weeks", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Where was everybody when she was on this chaotic, spiral downhill.", "answer_tokens": ["Where", "was", "everybody", "when", "she", "was", "on", "this", "chaotic", ",", "spiral", "downhill", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "What is happening while America sleeps?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "happening", "while", "America", "sleeps", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, you know, we were all surprised on 9/11.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "were", "all", "surprised", "on", "9/11", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Yes, but it's nowhere near, it's nowhere near in terms of financial firepower, anything like Mitt Romney's, and it kind of reminds me of that campaign Meg Whitman fought in California, because money in the end can't overcome personal deficiency, can it, as a candidate?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "nowhere", "near", ",", "it", "'s", "nowhere", "near", "in", "terms", "of", "financial", "firepower", ",", "anything", "like", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", ",", "and", "it", "kind", "of", "reminds", "me", "of", "that", "campaign", "Meg", "Whitman", "fought", "in", "California", ",", "because", "money", "in", "the", "end", "ca", "n't", "overcome", "personal", "deficiency", ",", "can", "it", ",", "as", "a", "candidate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Usually not.", "answer_tokens": ["Usually", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Meg Whitman"], "LOCATION": ["California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "I mean that is hypocritical, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "that", "is", "hypocritical", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "It really disappointed me and I was very clear about it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "really", "disappointed", "me", "and", "I", "was", "very", "clear", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Where do you think he's really been going wrong or where would you give him due credit?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "really", "been", "going", "wrong", "or", "where", "would", "you", "give", "him", "due", "credit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, if you really look at the book carefully, I'm far more favorable about the president than critical.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "really", "look", "at", "the", "book", "carefully", ",", "I", "'m", "far", "more", "favorable", "about", "the", "president", "than", "critical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "You're not feeling the surge?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "feeling", "the", "surge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "No, I'm really not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "really", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Steve, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Steve", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Steve.", "answer_tokens": ["Steve", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "You appeared how many times on Johnnie Carson?", "question_tokens": ["You", "appeared", "how", "many", "times", "on", "Johnnie", "Carson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "About 140 times.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "140", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnnie Carson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "That has to be a record, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "has", "to", "be", "a", "record", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes, Bob Hope was the most, and I was the second most.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Bob", "Hope", "was", "the", "most", ",", "and", "I", "was", "the", "second", "most", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Carousel"], "PERSON": ["Charlie Hartsock", "Vance DeGeneres"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", ":", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "What was the idea?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Well, Charlie Hartsock and Vance DeGeneres, who are my partners at Carousel, had this idea to kind of trace the -- trace comedy in terms of generations and -- and how it cross-pollinates and sort of look to people's inspirations.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Charlie", "Hartsock", "and", "Vance", "DeGeneres", ",", "who", "are", "my", "partners", "at", "Carousel", ",", "had", "this", "idea", "to", "kind", "of", "trace", "the", "--", "trace", "comedy", "in", "terms", "of", "generations", "and", "--", "and", "how", "it", "cross-pollinates", "and", "sort", "of", "look", "to", "people", "'s", "inspirations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "-- of superstar comedians, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "of", "superstar", "comedians", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 367, "question": "How are you -- how are you billing it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "--", "how", "are", "you", "billing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, I -- I don't know if it's a definitive history of comedy, but it is --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "it", "'s", "a", "definitive", "history", "of", "comedy", ",", "but", "it", "is", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "On what makes people laugh?", "question_tokens": ["On", "what", "makes", "people", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "It's unique in the way in which the comedians talk about what they do.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "unique", "in", "the", "way", "in", "which", "the", "comedians", "talk", "about", "what", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "That happened between you and him?", "question_tokens": ["That", "happened", "between", "you", "and", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "That never happened.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "never", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Is there a stat -- when you all get together?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "stat", "--", "when", "you", "all", "get", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "It's so subjective.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "so", "subjective", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Are you -- are you a funny person by nature?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "a", "funny", "person", "by", "nature", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "s it evidenced by this interview, no.", "answer_tokens": ["s", "it", "evidenced", "by", "this", "interview", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "But biggest comedian would your great burning ambition as a kid, was it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "biggest", "comedian", "would", "your", "great", "burning", "ambition", "as", "a", "kid", ",", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJS", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "And if it's funny, then, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "it", "'s", "funny", ",", "then", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Let's talk a little bit break, gents.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "talk", "a", "little", "bit", "break", ",", "gents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "But you do -- do you thank God every day that these things happen?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "do", "--", "do", "you", "thank", "God", "every", "day", "that", "these", "things", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "It's a little bit like that, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "little", "bit", "like", "that", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "There -- there is no Moe and Larry here.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "--", "there", "is", "no", "Moe", "and", "Larry", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "It will hide your own lack of character, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "will", "hide", "your", "own", "lack", "of", "character", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Arkin"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Who -- if I could trap you both on a desert island separately and you could have one comedian with you to make you laugh for the rest of your days, who would you take?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "--", "if", "I", "could", "trap", "you", "both", "on", "a", "desert", "island", "separately", "and", "you", "could", "have", "one", "comedian", "with", "you", "to", "make", "you", "laugh", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "days", ",", "who", "would", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I would take Alan Arkin.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "take", "Alan", "Arkin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Because he makes -- one-to-one, he makes me laugh more than anyone I've ever met.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "makes", "--", "one-to-one", ",", "he", "makes", "me", "laugh", "more", "than", "anyone", "I", "'ve", "ever", "met", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "He is -- he's so dry and so acerbic, he just -- I love being around the man.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "--", "he", "'s", "so", "dry", "and", "so", "acerbic", ",", "he", "just", "--", "I", "love", "being", "around", "the", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Who would you take?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "I'd probably take Groucho.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "probably", "take", "Groucho", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "If you're honest, did you prefer life before, when you were more anonymous, or have you actually embraced the whole fame thing with great enthusiasm?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "honest", ",", "did", "you", "prefer", "life", "before", ",", "when", "you", "were", "more", "anonymous", ",", "or", "have", "you", "actually", "embraced", "the", "whole", "fame", "thing", "with", "great", "enthusiasm", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "It's much, much better to be rich and famous.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "much", ",", "much", "better", "to", "be", "rich", "and", "famous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "I like to think it might have been, but you never know, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "like", "to", "think", "it", "might", "have", "been", ",", "but", "you", "never", "know", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "It's a lot tougher to deal with, I think, if you get that kind of thing when you're younger.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "lot", "tougher", "to", "deal", "with", ",", "I", "think", ",", "if", "you", "get", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "when", "you", "'re", "younger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Do you miss the character?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "miss", "the", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "do", "what", "Ricky", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Oh, not in a million years.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "not", "in", "a", "million", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "would", "just", "get", "too", "skittish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "You've got seven movies on the go, is that right, over the next two years?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "seven", "movies", "on", "the", "go", ",", "is", "that", "right", ",", "over", "the", "next", "two", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "ARELL: And I'm writing a symphony and I have a cooking show coming up.", "answer_tokens": ["ARELL", ":", "And", "I", "'m", "writing", "a", "symphony", "and", "I", "have", "a", "cooking", "show", "coming", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Did you ever imagine here you'd be in Hollywood in your smart power suit, in the middle of a seven movie extravaganza --", "answer_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "here", "you", "'d", "be", "in", "Hollywood", "in", "your", "smart", "power", "suit", ",", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "a", "seven", "movie", "extravaganza", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "-- earning you, potentially, a billion dollars?", "question_tokens": ["--", "earning", "you", ",", "potentially", ",", "a", "billion", "dollars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "A billion dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "billion", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "You must pinch yourself a bit, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "pinch", "yourself", "a", "bit", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "I'm always pinching myself.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "always", "pinching", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "You need to have had cigarettes burned on you for years, don't you, to be genuinely -- to make an audience laugh?", "question_tokens": ["You", "need", "to", "have", "had", "cigarettes", "burned", "on", "you", "for", "years", ",", "do", "n't", "you", ",", "to", "be", "genuinely", "--", "to", "make", "an", "audience", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", ":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "You said that Billy's timed to go with his Oscars appearance, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "said", "that", "Billy", "'s", "timed", "to", "go", "with", "his", "Oscars", "appearance", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "Eddie Murphy was probably doing it then, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Eddie", "Murphy", "was", "probably", "doing", "it", "then", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "It was before that.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "before", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eddie Murphy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}, "docId": "120220pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "I get the sense you've got great chemistry between you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "get", "the", "sense", "you", "'ve", "got", "great", "chemistry", "between", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "It's so -- I -- you know what, I think David is the best interviewer because he puts people at ease.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "so", "--", "I", "--", "you", "know", "what", ",", "I", "think", "David", "is", "the", "best", "interviewer", "because", "he", "puts", "people", "at", "ease", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]